<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://andrianllmm.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://andrianllmm.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-09-01T05:22:50+00:00</updated><id>https://andrianllmm.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Andrian Lloyd Maagma</title><subtitle>Andrian&apos;s personal website </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello, World!</title><link href="https://andrianllmm.github.io/blog/2024/hello-world/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello, World!"/><published>2024-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-08-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://andrianllmm.github.io/blog/2024/hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://andrianllmm.github.io/blog/2024/hello-world/"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my new digital space!</p> <p>Today marks an exciting milestone as I launch my very first <a href="https://andrianllmm.github.io">personal website</a>, built over the weekend using <a href="https://pages.github.com/">GitHub Pages</a> and <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll</a>. This site is going to be my little corner of the internet where I share my <a href="/projects">projects</a>, <a href="/publications">research</a>, <a href="/cv/#skills">skills</a>, and whatever else I’m interested in.</p> <p>Building this site is a big step for me. As someone who’s really into web dev, I wanted a space to present my work and connect with others who have similar interests. Here’s why I decided to create it:</p> <ul> <li> <p><strong>Show off my portfolio.</strong> I wanted an all-in-one place where friends, colleagues, collaborators, potential clients, and employers can easily explore my work and interests with just a single <a href="https://andrianllmm.github.io">click</a>. I felt that having my CV as a PDF, a separate LinkedIn profile, repositories and projects on GitHub, and research papers buried in my GDrive was a bit all over the place.</p> </li> <li> <p><strong>Learn static site generation.</strong> Building this site was a great way for me to get into static site generation with Jekyll. Since my past web dev projects were either plain HTML/CSS/JS or used backend frameworks like Django and Flask, it was a refreshing change to work with a static site generator. It felt like a nice middle ground between frontend-only and full-stack apps. I got to work with simple Markdown files instead of coding individual HTML pages like I used to. I also didn’t have to worry about a backend, since free hosting sites like GitHub Pages only support static files. It was also a quick process since I used a <a href="https://github.com/alshedivat/al-folio">template</a> as a starting point.</p> </li> <li> <p><strong>Practice writing and sharing content.</strong> I’ve been looking for a way to get better at technical writing and documenting my projects and ideas. This site is a great place to start. I’m not sure how often I’ll update the blog, but it’s a solid beginning in sharing what I’m doing and learning along the way.</p> </li> </ul> <p>Thanks for stopping by, and I hope you enjoy checking out my site as much as I enjoyed building it!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="personal"/><category term="programming"/><category term="productivity"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to my new digital space!]]></summary></entry></feed>